{
    "subject": "resource/Arnold_Schwarzenegger",
    "predicate": "property/termStart",
    "object": "2003-11-17",
    "human_readable": "The term start of Arnold Schwarzenegger is November 17, 2003.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9243289828300476,
            "question": "What is the context for November 17, 2003, related to Arnold Schwarzenegger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8365785479545593,
            "question": "When did Arnold Schwarzenegger's start?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8161874413490295,
            "question": "In what year did Arnold Schwarzenegger's start?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8050103783607483,
            "question": "What date is associated with the start of Arnold Schwarzenegger?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7880370616912842,
            "question": "Is November 17th significant in Arnold Schwarzenegger's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7182730436325073,
            "question": "What event marked the beginning of Arnold Schwarzenegger's career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6217972040176392,
            "question": "What accomplishments followed Arnold Schwarzenegger's start?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.595641553401947,
            "question": "Can you provide more information about what happened on November 17, 2003?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45487332344055176,
            "question": "How did Arnold Schwarzenegger's start influence his career trajectory?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25566068291664124,
            "question": "What does the term 'start' refer to in this case?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The term start of Arnold Schwarzenegger is November 17, 2003.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7995_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did Arnold Schwarzenegger's start influence his career trajectory?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7995_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide more information about what happened on November 17, 2003?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7995_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What accomplishments followed Arnold Schwarzenegger's start?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7995_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7995_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7995_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7995_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7995_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7995_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7995_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7995_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7995_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7995_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7995_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provided contain information about Arnold Schwarzenegger's governorship and career, which supports the statement that his term start is indeed November 17, 2003."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide information that Arnold Schwarzenegger was sworn in as the Governor of California on November 17, 2003. This supports the statement that his term started on this date."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}